[{"question": " listen y&#146;know what sir? for the last time, i don&#146;t care what the computer says, we did not take a bag of mashuga nuts from the mini-bar and we did not watch dr. do-me-a-little!", "answer": "  hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 1, "asentId": 2}, {"question": " oh! joey uh, were you in our room last night?", "answer": " no.  i was told the name of the movie would not appear on the bill!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 3, "asentId": 4}, {"question": "  hi! we&#146;re checking out of the bridal suite.", "answer": "  that&#146;s right. i&#146;m no longer a bride. i&#146;ll never be a bride again. now, i&#146;m just someone&#146;s wife!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 5, "asentId": 6}, {"question": " and i&#146;m the happiest guy in the world!  oh honey, come on don&#146;t be upset. we still have so much to look forward", "answer": " oh yeah, right.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 7, "asentId": 8}, {"question": " we got the honeymoon.", "answer": " that&#146;s not &#145;til thursday.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 9, "asentId": 10}, {"question": " the wedding pictures?", "answer": " they won&#146;t be ready for weeks.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 11, "asentId": 12}, {"question": " not the disposable cameras from the tables.", "answer": " that&#146;s true!  i knew i married you for a reason!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 13, "asentId": 14}, {"question": " i&#146;ll tell you what, i will go get them developed and you can go home.", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 15, "asentId": 16}, {"question": " what? what did you take a picture of?", "answer": " nothing! it was something.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 17, "asentId": 18}, {"question": " okay ross has the cameras, has he checked out yet?", "answer": " are you joking? check out is not &#145;til noon and he has a good  eleven minutes left.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 19, "asentId": 20}, {"question": " oh.", "answer": " ross has never checked out of a room a minute before he had to.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 21, "asentId": 22}, {"question": " yeah, one time, when we were dating, uh we got a late checkout, he got so excited it was the best sex we ever had. until y&#146;know, he screamed out radisson at the end.", "answer": " okay, well i&#146;m gonna get ross, get the cameras, and get them developed.  32 joe. you&#146;re 32!  front desk clerk:  here&#146;s a copy of your bill.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 23, "asentId": 24}, {"question": " oh thanks.  champagne, strawberries&#133;oh my god! i can&#146;t believe chandler ordered porn on our wedding night!", "answer": " yeah, that&#146;s sad. mashuga nut?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 25, "asentId": 26}, {"question": " hi.", "answer": " hey.  soaps? shampoos? are you really taking all this stuff?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 27, "asentId": 28}, {"question": " why not? it&#146;s built into the price of the room.", "answer": " yeah but you don&#146;t need&#151;&#151;what is this?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 29, "asentId": 30}, {"question": " thread!", "answer": " score! where are the disposable cameras?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 31, "asentId": 32}, {"question": " what disposable cameras?", "answer": " the cameras? remember last night i told you to take them?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 33, "asentId": 34}, {"question": " no you didn&#146;t.", "answer": " yes! remember? right before we cut the cake, i went up to you and i said&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 35, "asentId": 36}, {"question": " oh-oh yeah, you-you came up to me and asked if i could do you a favor, and my uncle murray came up to you and handed you a check. and then you said, &quot;why do they call it a check? why not a yugoslavian?&quot;  yeah, then you did that.", "answer": " so you don&#146;t have the cameras?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 37, "asentId": 38}, {"question": " no. sorry man.", "answer": " so? what? what? they&#146;re gone! monica&#146;s gonna freak!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 39, "asentId": 40}, {"question": " well, i&#146;m sure they&#146;re still somewhere here in the hotel. i&#146;ll-i&#146;ll help you look for them.", "answer": " great.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 41, "asentId": 42}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 45, "asentId": 46}, {"question": " are you gonna open the presents without chandler?", "answer": " no!  but, they&#146;re callin&#146; out to me! i mean this little guy  even crawled up into my lap. oh come on, chandler wouldn&#146;t mind if i opened just one present! what do you think it is?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 47, "asentId": 48}, {"question": " a tiny salt shaker!!!", "answer": " ohhh! my god! for tiny salt!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 51, "asentId": 52}, {"question": " oh wow! okay. well that was fun.", "answer": " oh yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 53, "asentId": 54}, {"question": " good. okay, i&#146;m just gonna wait for chandler to open the rest of them.", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 55, "asentId": 56}, {"question": " whew. although y&#146;know, this is part of a salt and pepper set. i mean&#133; i guess y&#146;know it may just count as a half a present. what do you think?", "answer": " well i guess it&#146;s okay to open one more if it&#146;s part of a set. y&#146;know, it&#146;s probably this one.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 57, "asentId": 58}, {"question": "  hi.", "answer": " hey, how are you feelin&#146;? any morning sickness?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 61, "asentId": 62}, {"question": " shh-shh-shh! the guys don&#146;t know yet do they?", "answer": " no! joey and ross don&#146;t know anything and chandler still thinks that phoebe&#146;s pregnant.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 63, "asentId": 64}, {"question": " yeah that&#146;s right chandler does still think i&#146;m pregnant. he hasn&#146;t asked me how i&#146;m feeling or offered to carry my bags. boy, i feel bad for the woman who ends up with him.  after you of course.", "answer": " don&#146;t worry i promise that you will only have to be pregnant for a few more hours, &#145;cause i&#146;m going to tell the father today.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 65, "asentId": 66}, {"question": " ooh, is it someone in this building? is it that tall guy from the first floor?", "answer": " ew! no!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 67, "asentId": 68}, {"question": " what?! i think he&#146;s cute.", "answer": " well then you have his baby.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 69, "asentId": 70}, {"question": " believe me i&#146;m trying.", "answer": " wow. y&#146;know it is so weird. i mean, you&#146;re gonna tell this guy today and he has no idea what&#146;s gonna happen.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 71, "asentId": 72}, {"question": " yeah. you&#146;re just gonna knock on his door and change his life forever. you&#146;re like ed mcmahon except without the big check, or the raw sexual magnetism.", "answer": " yeah. uh-huh, i guess it is pretty big news.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 73, "asentId": 74}, {"question": " pretty big? it&#146;s huge! god, this guy doesn&#146;t have a clue! he&#146;s just walking down the street thinking, &#145;i had sex with rachel green. i rock!&#146; then bam! he&#146;s a father and everything&#146;s different.", "answer": " well it&#146;s only different if he wants it to be. i mean, i&#146;m not gonna ask him for anything.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 75, "asentId": 76}, {"question": " okay. then he still has this huge decision to make. now he&#146;s walking around thinking, &#145;do i want to be a dad?&#146; and then bam!", "answer": " what was that bam?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 77, "asentId": 78}, {"question": " i don&#146;t. he got&#133;he-he-he-he&#146;s hit by a bus.", "answer": "  hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 79, "asentId": 80}, {"question": " hey joey, what would you do if someone that you slept with told you that she was pregnant?", "answer": "  who called here? did she sound blond? huh? did-did-did she have an accent? i gotta make a call!  i shoulda never walked into that sunglass hut!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 81, "asentId": 82}, {"question": " oh joey! joey! no, it&#146;s not you! you didn&#146;t get anybody pregnant!", "answer": " oh. why would you scare me like that? what the hell is going on?  is somebody pregnant?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 83, "asentId": 84}, {"question": " oh yeah. that&#146;s me.", "answer": " oh my god pheebs! you&#146;re gonna have a baby?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 85, "asentId": 86}, {"question": " whoa, wait a minute. who&#146;s the father?", "answer": " you don&#146;t know him. it&#146;s not important. he wants nothing to do with me or the baby.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 89, "asentId": 90}, {"question": " well who is this guy?! huh? who is he? &#145;cause i will track him down and kick his ass!", "answer": " david lynn.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 91, "asentId": 92}, {"question": " who&#146;s david lynn?", "answer": " oh some guy from my gym. a little annoying.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 95, "asentId": 96}, {"question": " chandler?", "answer": " hey! did you find the cameras?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 97, "asentId": 98}, {"question": " no. did you?", "answer": " yes! and that&#146;s why i&#146;m under the table. celebrating.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 99, "asentId": 100}, {"question": " well i checked in the uh, lost and found, i talked to the manager, no-one&#146;s turned them.", "answer": " well this is great. y&#146;know, those cameras were the only thing that was gonna cheer monica up today, she&#146;s really depressed.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 101, "asentId": 102}, {"question": " now you guys just got married, why is she so depressed?", "answer": " all my energy is going into not asking that question. i can&#146;t believe i screwed this up!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 103, "asentId": 104}, {"question": " i&#146;m sorry man.  here&#146;s a thought. this is the same ballroom. there&#146;s a band. there&#146;s gonna be plenty of dressed up people.", "answer": " are you suggesting we dance our troubles away?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 105, "asentId": 106}, {"question": " no-no-no, i&#146;m saying we-we buy more of this  at the gift shop, throw our tuxes back on, and take a few pictures. all we have to do is make sure not to get anybody else&#146;s faces.", "answer": " are you serious?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 107, "asentId": 108}, {"question": " i&#146;m just thinking about your new bride at home. okay? do-do you really want to start your life together by letting her down?", "answer": " marriage advice? really?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 109, "asentId": 110}, {"question": " i&#146;m telling you, this looks exactly like your wedding! aren&#146;t these the same flowers?", "answer": " i don&#146;t know, monica picked out the flowers.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 111, "asentId": 112}, {"question": " what about the chairs?", "answer": " she picked those out too.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 113, "asentId": 114}, {"question": " how about the place settings?", "answer": " that was her.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 115, "asentId": 116}, {"question": " what did you do?", "answer": " i was in charge of the cameras! gift shop?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 117, "asentId": 118}, {"question": " hey! ooh, did you do it yet?", "answer": " not yet.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 121, "asentId": 122}, {"question": " oh, well what are you doing here? are you about to do it?  is it gunther?", "answer": " no! phoebe, it&#146;s not gunther.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 123, "asentId": 124}, {"question": " thank god, &#145;cause that hair on a baby&#133;", "answer": " phoebe the father is not here okay? i haven&#146;t told him yet and i don&#146;t think i can tell him at all now!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 125, "asentId": 126}, {"question": " why not?", "answer": " i don&#146;t know, let me think. i was walking down the street thinking, &#145;i&#146;m gonna tell the father today&#146; and then bam!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 127, "asentId": 128}, {"question": " bus?", "answer": " no, you! phoebe you freaked me out. you kept saying how huge this all", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 129, "asentId": 130}, {"question": " well-well but it is huge.", "answer": " i know, but i was just thinking about how huge this is for me. i didn&#146;t even go to how huge this was going to be for the father.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 131, "asentId": 132}, {"question": "  ooh-ooh-ooh! are we opening presents?", "answer": " no! no! i shouldn&#146;t have even opened these! i mean i&#151;joey i am out of control!! joey, you have to do me a favor. no matter what i say, no matter what i do, please do not let me open another present! okay?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 135, "asentId": 136}, {"question": " okay.", "answer": " give me one more.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 137, "asentId": 138}, {"question": "  hey.", "answer": " oh good, uh you&#146;re here. uh pheebs? listen uh sit down. i-i got something i want to say.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 141, "asentId": 142}, {"question": " umm, now uh&#133; it&#146;s a scary world out there, especially for a single mom. y&#146;know, now i always thought you and i had a special bond so&#133;  phoebe buffay, will you marry me?", "answer": " oh my god! joey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 145, "asentId": 146}, {"question": " you can&#146;t marry him!", "answer": " hey lady, your day&#146;s over! it&#146;s my turn!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 149, "asentId": 150}, {"question": " phoebe!", "answer": " why?! why can&#146;t she marry me?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 151, "asentId": 152}, {"question": " she&#146;s not pregnant. it&#146;s rachel. rachel&#146;s the one who&#146;s pregnant.", "answer": " oh my god.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 155, "asentId": 156}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " phoebe i think he would notice if you didn&#146;t have a baby in nine months!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 157, "asentId": 158}, {"question": "  now i can&#146;t believe it! what? rachel&#146;s pregnant?  who&#146;s the father?", "answer": " we don&#146;t know.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 161, "asentId": 162}, {"question": " ohh&#133; i wonder if that dude.", "answer": " there&#146;s a dude?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 163, "asentId": 164}, {"question": " yeah.", "answer": " who? who is it?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 165, "asentId": 166}, {"question": " the guy left this.", "answer": "  oh my god! i know who the father is&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 171, "asentId": 172}, {"question": "  uh, excuse me? could you take a picture of us? woman at the wedding: oh! of course.  man at the wedding: uh, would you take one of us?", "answer": " uhh&#133; yeah sure.  click! woman at the wedding: it didn&#146;t click.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 175, "asentId": 176}, {"question": " i heard it. i heard it. man at the wedding: but there was no flash. woman at the wedding: why won&#146;t you take our picture?", "answer": " oh yeah. i&#146;ll take, i&#146;ll take your picture.  man at the wedding: uh, your finger was covering the lens.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 177, "asentId": 178}, {"question": " look, i feel really bad about how i freaked you out before, so i called the father and asked him to meet you here so you can tell him. go!", "answer": " what? hey wait a minute! phoebe, how do you even know who the father is?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 181, "asentId": 182}, {"question": " i may play the fool at times, but i&#146;m a little more than a pretty blond girl with an ass that won&#146;t quit.  i believe this belongs to the father of your baby.", "answer": " oh god&#133; oh, he&#146;s in there right now?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 183, "asentId": 184}, {"question": " uh-huh. now you can turn around or you can go in there and rip the band-aid off. what to you want to do?", "answer": " uh, let&#146;s rip!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 185, "asentId": 186}, {"question": " really? are you sure?", "answer": " oh phoebe!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 187, "asentId": 188}, {"question": " why don&#146;t you go up on stage. i&#146;ll get a picture of you doing the speech.", "answer": " okay. okay!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 193, "asentId": 194}, {"question": " will the owner of a 1995 buick lesabre please see the front desk? your car is about to be towed. anxious wedding guest:  that&#146;s my car!", "answer": " a &#146;95 lesabre?! anxious wedding guest: yes!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 195, "asentId": 196}, {"question": " a green lesabre? anxious wedding guest: yes!", "answer": " i&#146;m sorry, i meant a blue lesabre. anxious wedding guest: yes! green-blue!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 197, "asentId": 198}, {"question": " okay, you ready for the last picture?", "answer": " yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 201, "asentId": 202}, {"question": " so, what&#146;s this about?", "answer": " rachel has something that she wants to tell you and umm, i believe that this is your red sweater.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 205, "asentId": 206}, {"question": " no.  this is my red sweater.", "answer": " oh no. could i get anyone a coffee or&#133;poison? no? just for me? okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 207, "asentId": 208}, {"question": " what&#146;s going on rach?", "answer": " nothing! phoebe kinda made a mistake. but y&#146;know you do wear that sweater a lot, are you involved in some kind of dare?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 209, "asentId": 210}, {"question": " y&#146;know, i&#146;m actually glad phoebe called.  i know we broke up because you thought i wasn&#146;t mature enough, but i&#146;ve really grown up and think we should get back together.", "answer": " oh, it&#146;s just not the right time.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 211, "asentId": 212}, {"question": " okay.", "answer": " i&#146;m ready for more.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 215, "asentId": 216}, {"question": " tag&#133;", "answer": " come on rach, let&#146;s give it another try.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 217, "asentId": 218}, {"question": " i&#146;m having a baby.", "answer": " oh.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 219, "asentId": 220}, {"question": " you can go.", "answer": " thank you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 221, "asentId": 222}, {"question": "  i don&#146;t know how any of these got opened?!", "answer": "  you opened them all?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 223, "asentId": 224}, {"question": " i know! i know! i am a terrible person! i mean, chandler is never going to trust me with anything ever again!", "answer": " oh hey! you got my parent&#146;s gift!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 225, "asentId": 226}, {"question": " yeah. what is that?", "answer": " well, i don&#146;t know. i think it does something to salami.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 227, "asentId": 228}, {"question": " hey! how&#146;d it go?", "answer": " yeah. what-what did tag say?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 229, "asentId": 230}, {"question": " tag is not the father! and joey knows now?", "answer": " i do rach. i do, and i so happy for you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 231, "asentId": 232}, {"question": " oh wow, you didn&#146;t even try to unhook my bra!", "answer": " so are you ever gonna tell whoever it is?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 233, "asentId": 234}, {"question": " no, i will. i&#146;m just not up for it tonight.", "answer": " hey rach listen, no matter what this guy says i want you to know you&#146;re not gonna be alone in this.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 235, "asentId": 236}, {"question": " i&#146;m not?", "answer": " listen i uh&#133;  it&#146;s a scary world out there especially if you&#146;re a single mom. y&#146;know, i always felt like you and i have this-this special bond. y&#146;know? so,  rachel green will you marry me?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 237, "asentId": 238}, {"question": " what?", "answer": " what?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 239, "asentId": 240}, {"question": " what?!!", "answer": " pheebs, give me the ring back!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 241, "asentId": 242}, {"question": " no!!", "answer": " no! joey, oh you&#146;re so sweet. you&#146;re so-so sweet, honey. but i&#146;m not, i&#146;m not looking for a husband.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 243, "asentId": 244}, {"question": "  i understand.", "answer": " now, if you will excuse me i am going to go and lie down.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 245, "asentId": 246}, {"question": " i can&#146;t say that didn&#146;t hurt. but i&#146;ll take you back joey tribbiani.", "answer": " uh yeah. pheebs, listen about that. i only offered&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 247, "asentId": 248}, {"question": " ooh! a salami buddy!", "answer": " there you go!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 249, "asentId": 250}, {"question": " we&#146;re back!", "answer": " great! we&#146;re hangin&#146; in the kitchen!  let&#146;s stay in the kitchen!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 251, "asentId": 252}, {"question": " it&#146;s picture time.", "answer": " now you are going to love these.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 253, "asentId": 254}, {"question": "  here&#146;s a picture of ross.  and that&#146;s me.  and that&#146;s me and ross.  oh-ho, that is a picture of our first kiss as a married couple.", "answer": " wow! that is a great picture!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 255, "asentId": 256}, {"question": " eh?", "answer": " yeah! oh and interesting because i found the cameras in one of our bags!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 257, "asentId": 258}, {"question": " huh, didn&#146;t see that coming.", "answer": " okay, so this isn&#146;t a picture of our first, but it is a picture of my first kiss with&#133;with this lady. which by the look on your face i&#146;m sure you&#146;ll remember. so we don&#146;t need&#151;&#151;there&#146;s no need to have this picture. how about i take the real pictures and get them developed right now.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 259, "asentId": 260}, {"question": " that would be a good idea.", "answer": " okay.  you opened all the presents without me?! i thought we were supposed to do that together!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 261, "asentId": 262}, {"question": " you kissed another woman!", "answer": " call it even?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 263, "asentId": 264}, {"question": " well, i&#146;m gonna go get these  in some water.", "answer": " wait you stole those from these people&#146;s wedding?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 267, "asentId": 268}, {"question": " no-no, i took them from the hotel lobby. yeah, they think they can charge me for some dirty movie and a bag of mashuga nuts, they got another think coming.  hey! my sweater! i&#146;ve been looking for this for like a month!  monica and phoebe: oh my god!!", "answer": "  oh my god!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 269, "asentId": 270}, {"question": " hey! how you doing?", "answer": " good! good, long time no see.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 271, "asentId": 272}, {"question": " yeah.", "answer": " like your sweater.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 273, "asentId": 274}, {"question": " oh hey, right back at ya.", "answer": " oh, it&#146;s crazy about rachel huh?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 275, "asentId": 276}, {"question": " yeah. she&#151;well, she&#146;s one crazy lady?", "answer": " so whose is it?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 277, "asentId": 278}, {"question": "  umm, i don&#146;t some italian guy. come on, read your own label. see you later.", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 279, "asentId": 280}]